Inventory of the George Haven Putnam papers, circa 1800-1931
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- CORRESPONDENCE:
  - Putnam to Colonel Roosevelt., 11-4--1918 (Box 8)
  - Putnam? to Theodore (Col. Roosevelt)., 12-4-1918 (Box 8)
  - Putnam, The American Rights League, to Colonel Roosevelt., 12-4-1918 (Box 8)
  - Theodore Roosevelt to Major Putnam. Photo-copy., 12-5-1918 (Box 8)
  - Theodore Roosevelt to Major Putnam. 2 copies., 12-5-1918 (Box 8)
  - William Howard Taft to Major Putnam., 12-9-1918 (Box 8)
  - William Howard Taft to Major Putnam., 12-23-1918 (Box 8)
  - Henry Cabot Lodge to Mr. Putnam., 12-27-1918 (Box 8)
  - Archibald B. Roosevelt to Major Putnam., 1-20-1919 (Box 8)
  - Elihu Root to Haven., 1-22-1919 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Mrs. Roosevelt., 1-23-1919 (Box 8)
  - Henry Cabot Lodge to Mr. Putnam., 1-25-1919 (Box 8)
  - Elihu Root to Putnam., 2-24-1919 (Box 8)
  - Henry Morgenthau to Mr. Putnam., 2-28-1919 (Box 8)
  - William R. Mayer to Major Putnam., 3-14-1919 (Box 8)
  - William Howard Taft to Major Putnam., 3-9-1919 (Box 8)
  - S. L. Parrish to Major Putnam., 3-17-1919 (Box 8)
  - Elihu Root to Putnam., 4-3-1919 (Box 8)
  - John W. Davis to Major Putnam., 6-12-1919 (Box 8)
  - Jusserand to Putnam., 9-19-1919 (Box 8)
  - Askwith to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 10-12-1919 (Box 8)
  - William Howard Taft to Major Putnam. 2 copies., 12-4-1919 (Box 8)
  - Suarte Anheinis to Putnam's Sons Ltd., 12-6-1919 (Box 8)
  - Theodore Roosevelt to Major Putnam., 1-4-1920 (Box 8)
  - L. Rand to Mr. Putnam., 1-8-1920 (Box 8)
  - William T. Manning to Major Putnam., 1-10-1920 (Box 8)
  - Theodore Roosevelt to Mr. Putnam., 1-12-1920 (Box 8)
  - Charles W. Eliot to Major Putnam., 2-3-1920 (Box 8)
  - Florence S. Barclay to Major Putnam., 2-7-1920 (Box 8)
  - Hitchcock to Mr. Putnam., 2-26-1920 (Box 8)
  - Elihu Root to Major., 3-6-1920 (Box 8)
  - Ernest M. Stires to Major Putnam., 3-12-1920 (Box 8)
  - Harriet B. Audubon to Mr. Putnam., 3-12-1920 (Box 8)
  - Arthur B. Miller to Major., 4-20-1920 (Box 8)
  - James Bryce to Major Putnam., 6-23-1920 (Box 8)
  - Henry L. Stimson to Major Putnam., 7-14-1920 (Box 8)
  - John J. Parshing to Major Putnam., 8-17-1920 (Box 8)
  - From H. G. Wells. Postcard., 9-8-1920 (Box 8)
  - H_ther to Major Putnam., 9-21-1920 (Box 8)
  - Isabell Stewart to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 9-24-1920 (Box 8)
  - A. P. Brigham to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 9-28-1920 (Box 8)
  - Henry A. Stimson to Mr. Putnam., 10-16-1920 (Box 8)
  - Edith Kennit Roosevelt to Mr. Putnam., 11-5-1920 (Box 8)
  - Lawrence F. Abbott to Major., 11-9-1920 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Lieut.-Colonel Theodore Roosevelt., 12-15-1920 (Box 8)
  - Edward W. Bok to Mr. Putnam., 1-6-1921 (Box 8)
  - From John Edwin Sandys., 2-4-1921 (Box 8)
  - William T. Manning to Mr. Putnam., 2-7-1921 (Box 8)
  - William T. Manning to Major Putnam., 2-9-1921 (Box 8)
  - From S_eater Cou_t_l to Major Putnam., 2-11-1921 (Box 8)
  - To Charles Park., 2-24-1921 (Box 8)
  - Richard Sadlen to Major Putnam., 3-10-1921 (Box 8)
  - Ankwith to Major Putnam., 5-11-1921 (Box 8)
  - Mills and Boon, Ltd., Publishers, to Major Putnam., 5-14-1921 (Box 8)
  - The Morning Post to Major Putnam., 5-23-1921 (Box 8)
  - J. St. _ Strachey to Putnam., 5-28-1921 (Box 8)
  - _ed_wood Bern to Major Putnam., 6-1-1921 (Box 8)
  - William S. Sims to Major., 6-21-1921 (Box 8)
  - Anna C. Maxwell to Major Putnam., 7-12-1921 (Box 8)
  - James Freem_ Cooper to Mr. Putnam., 7-17-1921 (Box 8)
  - To Lawrence F. Abbott., 8-8-1921 (Box 8)
  - Albert Berry Bringham to Mr. Taylor., 8-23-1921 (Box 8)
  - Marie C. Stopes to Major and Mrs. Putnam., 10-29-1921 (Box 8)
  - Mr. Duster to Mr. Putnam., 12-14-1921 (Box 8)
  - Henry Holt to GHP and EJP., 1-7-1922 (Box 8)
  - V. Stefansson to Major Putnam., 1-18-1922 (Box 8)
  - Herbert S. Hadley to George Haven Putnam., 2-11-1922 (Box 8)
  - Astin to Mr. Putnam., 4-23-1922 (Box 8)
  - Satis M. Coleman to Major Putnam., 4-25-1922 (Box 8)
  - Nan_ Antis to Mr. Putnam., 4-27-1922 (Box 8)
  - Ra_ B_bie to Major Putnam., 5-1-1922 (Box 8)
  - Gifford Pinchot to Major Putnam., 6-15-1922 (Box 8)
  - Charles E. Hughes to Mr. Putnam., 8-19-1922 (Box 8)
  - Fa_derlip to Major Putnam., 9-22-1922 (Box 8)
  - William Howard Taft to George Haven Putnam., 9-27-1922 (Box 8)
  - Charles E. Jefferson to Mr. Putnam., 10-24-1922 (Box 8)
  - From Lawrence F. Abbott., 11-13-1922 (Box 8)
  - Dwight E. Marion to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 11-30-1922 (Box 8)
  - Arthur Curtiss James to Mr. Putnam., 12-26-1922 (Box 8)
  - J. St. Loe Strachey to Mr. Grubb., 1-29-1923 (Box 8)
  - C. A. James to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 2-1-1923 (Box 8)
  - R. to Grubb., 2-8-1923 (Box 8)
  - Strachey to Putnam., 2-8-1923 (Box 8)
  - William O. Straddard to Mr. Putnam., 2-23-1923 (Box 8)
  - Alec Waugh to Grubb., 2-27-1923 (Box 8)
  - Anna G. Reginald to Major Putnam., 3-9-1923 (Box 8)
  - Dorothy Mills to Major Putnam., 3-15-1923 (Box 8)
  - Helen Fizedlaender to Mr. Grubb., 3-22-1923 (Box 8)
  - Charles W. Bierson to Major Putnam., 3-20-1923 (Box 8)
  - Robert Lynd to G. H. Grubb., 3-22-1923 (Box 8)
  - L. E. Robinson to Mr. Putnam., 4-14-1923 (Box 8)
  - G. O. to Mr. Putnam., 5-9-1923 (Box 8)
  - H. D. Johnston to Mr. Huntington., 5-30-1923 (Box 8)
  - Hall Caine to Major Putnam., 7-5-1923 (Box 8)
  - Elinor Mordant to Mr. Grubb., 7-30-1923 (Box 8)
  - Franklin K. Young to Maj. George Haven Putnam., 8-7-1923 (Box 8)
  - George W. Westinham to Major., 9-7-1923 (Box 8)
  - Robert Ceiyl to Mr. Putnam., 9-8-1923 (Box 8)
  - Lawrence P. Abbott to Major Puntam., 10-6-1923 (Box 8)
  - A. Eyre Machlin to Mr. Grubb., 10-19-1923 (Box 8)
  - Phillip G. Clifford to Major Puntam., 10-19-1923 (Box 8)
  - J. E. Hammsworth to Mr. Grubb., 10-19-1923 (Box 8)
  - Frank Newnes to Mr. Grubb., 10-26-1923 (Box 8)
  - Elihu Root to Major., 11-5-1923 (Box 8)
  - G. M. Trevelyan to Putnam., 11-29-1923 (Box 8)
  - Jusserand to Putnam., 1-29-1924 (Box 8)
  - John Drinkwater to Mr. Grubb., 2-5-1924 (Box 8)
  - Ha_ Begbie to Putnam., 2-15-1924 (Box 8)
  - Charles G. Wheeler to Mr. MacCillivray., 2-16-1924 (Box 8)
  - Charles W. Eliot to Mr. Putnam., 3-15-1924 (Box 8)
  - W. A. MacHortle to Major Putnam., 3-20-1924 (Box 8)
  - Charles Hughes to Mr. Putnam., 4-21-1924 (Box 8)
  - Buckmaster to Mrs. Putnam., 5-6-1924 (Box 8)
  - P. D. to Major Putnam., 5-10-1924 (Box 8)
  - H. Bellor to Major Putnam., 5-17-1924 (Box 8)
  - H. Begbie to Putnam., 5-18-1924 (Box 8)
  - From M. Benson., 6-7-1924 (Box 8)
  - John W. Davis to Major Putnam., 6-26-1924 (Box 8)
  - John C. Soley to Mr. Putnam., 8-1-1924 (Box 8)
  - John W. Davis to Maj. Putnam., 8-2-1924 (Box 8)
  - Caroleyn Houghton to Mr. Putnam., 9-9-1924 (Box 8)
  - Davis Morton to Major Putnam., 10-15-1924 (Box 8)
  - Stuart P. Shurman to Mr. Putnam., 9-26-1924 (Box 8)
  - Jusserand to Putnam., 10-24-1924 (Box 8)
  - Walter Damrosch to Putnam., 11-1-1924 (Box 8)
  - Elizabeth Goldsmith to Major Putnam., 11-3-1924 (Box 8)
  - John W. Davis to Major Putnam., 11-7-1924 (Box 8)
  - Charles W. Eliot to Mr. Putnam., 11-7-1924 (Box 8)
  - Henry van Dyke to Major., 11-11-1924 (Box 8)
  - H. Beller to Major Putnam., 12-3-1924 (Box 8)
  - J. St. Lee Strachey to Putnam., 12-5-1924 (Box 8)
  - Frederick Tupper to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 2-7-1925 (Box 8)
  - Helen Tyler Brown to Major Putnam., 2-16-1925 (Box 8)
  - Frederick Tupper to Major Putnam., 2-17-1925 (Box 8)
  - John W. Davis to Major., 4-7-1925 (Box 8)
  - Dorothy Mills to Major Putnam., 5-10-1925 (Box 8)
  - Irving Howbert to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 8-13-1925 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Editor, the Sunday Magazine., 8-21-1925 (Box 8)
  - Charles G. Wheeler to G. P. Putnam's Sons., 9-5-1925 (Box 8)
  - Stuart Sherman to Major Putnam., 9-5-1925 (Box 8)
  - John Jay Chapman to Putnam., 12-20-1925 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Editor of the "Spectator.", 12-28-1925 (Box 8)
  - Walter Seton to Major Putnam., 1-1-1926 (Box 8)
  - Nether_ to Major Putnam., 1-3-1926 (Box 8)
  - M. Storey to Putnam., 1-20-1926 (Box 8)
  - Joseph Culling to Major Putnam., 1-28-1926 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to the Editor, The Forum., 3-20-1926 (Box 8)
  - John W. Davis to Major., 5-18-1926 (Box 8)
  - D. W. Holmes to Mr. Putnam., 8-21-1926 (Box 8)
  - William S. Sims to Major Putnam., 11-1-1926 (Box 8)
  - A. A. Seton to Major Putnam., 11-10-1926 (Box 8)
  - Carter Glass to Putnam., 11-16-1926 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Don. John W. Davis., 12-13-1926 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to J. Lawrence Lowell., 12-14-1926 (Box 8)
  - Nicholas Murray Butley to Lord Loch., 12-14-1926 (Box 8)
  - John W. Davis to Major., 12-14-1926 (Box 8)
  - Walter Seton to Major Putnam., 12-14-1926 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to J. Lawrence Lowell., 12-15-1926 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Frank J. Goodnow., 12-15-1926 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Walter Warren Seton., 12-15-1926 (Box 8)
  - From Herbert Spencer Hadley., 12-16-1926 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Edwin Anderson Alderman., 12-16-1926 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to James R. Angell., 12-16-1926 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Arthur T. Hadley., 12-16-1926 (Box 8)
  - E. A. Alderman to Mr. Putnam., 12-17-1926 (Box 8)
  - Edith Briggs to Miss Damow., 12-18-1926 (Box 8)
  - Frank Aydelotte to Major Putnam., 12-20-1926 (Box 8)
  - Lincoln Cromwell to Mr. Putnam., 12-20-1926 (Box 8)
  - George W. Wi_sham to Major., 12-20-1926 (Box 8)
  - Frank J. Goodman to Mr. Putnam., 12-20-1926 (Box 8)
  - F. R. Coudert to Major Putnam., 12-20-1926 (Box 8)
  - Josiah H. Persimmon to Mr. Putnam., 12-21-1926 (Box 8)
  - John G. Hibben to Major Putnam., 12-21-1926 (Box 8)
  - James R. Angell to Mr. Putnam., 12-21-1926 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to John Daniels., 12-22-1926 (Box 8)
  - Herbert S. Hadley to Major Putnam., 12-22-1926 (Box 8)
  - Cass Gilbert to Major., 12-22-1926 (Box 8)
  - W. W. Cazman to Mr. Putnam., 12-23-1926 (Box 8)
  - William D. Guthrie to Major Putnam., 12-23-1926 (Box 8)
  - John Daniells to Major Putnam., 12-23-1926 (Box 8)
  - Valentine E. Macy Jr. to George Haven Putnam., 12-24-1926 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Professor Walter W. Seton., 12-24-1926 (Box 8)
  - Henry Osborn Taylor to Major., 12-26-1926 (Box 8)
  - E. H. Outerbridge to Gen. Putnam., 12-27-1926 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to George Edwin Maclean., 12-27-1926 (Box 8)
  - Hamilton Holt to Mr. Putnam., 12-27-1926 (Box 8)
  - John A. Stewart to Major Putnam., 12-28-1926 (Box 8)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt to Major Putnam., 12-28-1926 (Box 8)
  - William Church Osborn to Major Putnam., 12-28-1926 (Box 8)
  - F. P. Keppel to Major Putnam., 12-29-1926 (Box 8)
  - Theodore Roosevelt to Major Putnam., 12-29-1926 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to John Daniels., 12-29-1926 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Professor W. W. Seton., 12-30-1926 (Box 8)
  - T. W. Laurant to Major Putnam., 12-30-1926 (Box 8)
  - John Daniels to Major Putnam., 12-30-1926 (Box 8)
  - Elihu Root to Major., 12-30-1926 (Box 8)
  - Arthur T. Hadley to Major Putnam., 12-30-1926 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Hon. David Jayne Hill., 12-31-1926 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to James G. Parsons., 1-4-1927 (Box 8)
  - _inn Gabriel to Major Putnam., 1-5-1927 (Box 8)
  - David J. Hill to Major Putnam., 1-5-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Lt. Col Vivian Gabriel., 1-6-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Hon. Charles R. Hughes, 1-6-1927 (Box 8)
  - Olmsted Brothers to George Haven Putnam., 1-7-1927 (Box 8)
  - M. G. MacDonald to Major Putnam., 1-7-1927 (Box 8)
  - Charles E. Hughes to Mr. Putnam., 1-8-1927 (Box 8)
  - Theodore Collier to Mr. Putnam., 1-8-1927 (Box 8)
  - Vivian Gabriel to Major Putnam., 1-10-1927 (Box 8)
  - Thomas B. Appleget to Mr. Putnam., 1-10-1927 (Box 8)
  - Earl Russell Fish to Mr. Putnam., 1-10-1927 (Box 8)
  - Ruth Pratt to Major Putnam., 1-10-1927 (Box 8)
  - Charles R. Lingley to Mr. Putnam., 1-10-1927 (Box 8)
  - Laurence M. Larson to Putnam., 1-10-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Professor J. Franklin Jameson., 1-10-1927 (Box 8)
  - Henry Moir to Major Putnam., 1-10-1927 (Box 8)
  - Agnes Cromwell to Mr. Putnam., 1-11-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Richard Welling., 1-11-1927 (Box 8)
  - W. W. Seton to Major Putnam., 1-11-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to W. R. Hearst., 1-11-1927 (Box 8)
  - J. P. Morgan to Mr. Putnam., 1-11-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Arthur Brisbane., 1-11-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to C. H. Vantyne., 1-12-1927 (Box 8)
  - J. Franklin Jameson to Major Putnam., 1-13-1927 (Box 8)
  - J. St. Lee Strachey to Putnam., 1-15-1927 (Box 8)
  - A. Brisbane to Mr. Putnam., 1-17-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Professor Seton., 1-18-1927 (Box 8)
  - James A. Woodburn to Mr. Putnam., 1-18-1927 (Box 8)
  - Jackson for Lady Astor to Putnam., 1-19-1927 (Box 8)
  - Theodore Marburg to Major Putnam., 1-21-1927 (Box 8)
  - Davis Y. Thomas to Mr. Putnam., 1-21-1927 (Box 8)
  - A. E. McKinley to Mr. Putnam., 1-24-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Professor Walter W. Seton., 1-24-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Otto H. Kahn., 1-25-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Hon. John W. Davis., 1-25-1927 (Box 8)
  - Ethel Paine to Mr. Putnam., 1-26-1927 (Box 8)
  - Henry Fairfield Osborn to George Haven Putnam., 1-31-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Hon. John W. Davis., 1-27-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam Professor Saton., 1-27-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Strachey., 1-27-1927 (Box 8)
  - Otto H. Kahn to Major Putnam., 1-28-1927 (Box 8)
  - Arthur W. Page to Major Putnam., 1-28-1927 (Box 8)
  - Mary E. Woolley to Mr. Putnam., 1-29-1927 (Box 8)
  - A. C. McLaughlin to Mr. Putnam., 1-29-1927 (Box 8)
  - Virginia C. Gildenster to Major Putnam., 1-29-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Otto H. Kahn., 1-29-1927 (Box 8)
  - S. Stanwood Menken to Mr. Putnam., 1-31-1927 (Box 8)
  - Adolph S. Ochs to Mr. Putnam., 1-31-1927 (Box 8)
  - Otto Kahn to Major Putnam., 1-31-1927 (Box 8)
  - J. Edwin G_ for James Brown Scott to Putnam., 1-31-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Kahn., 2-1-1927 (Box 8)
  - Clarence H. Mackay to Putnam., 2-2-1927 (Box 8)
  - William L. Manning to Putnam., 2-2-1927 (Box 8)
  - Helen C. Lukens to Mr. Putnam., 2-2-1927 (Box 8)
  - Vivian Gabriel to Putnam., 2-2-1927 (Box 8)
  - Henry H. Flayden to Mr. Putnam., 2-2-1927 (Box 8)
  - Evelyn Wrench to Major Putnam., 2-2-1927 (Box 8)
  - Elmer E. Brown to Major Putnam., 2-2-1927 (Box 8)
  - William H. Baldwin to Major Putnam., 2-2-1927 (Box 8)
  - George E. MacLean to Mr. Putnam., 2-3-1927 (Box 8)
  - Charles E. Hughes to Major Putnam., 2-3-1927 (Box 8)
  - Owen D. Young to Mr. Putnam., 2-3-1927 (Box 8)
  - Theodore Collier to Major Putnam., 2-3-1927 (Box 8)
  - A. E. McKinley to Major Putnam., 2-3-1927 (Box 8)
  - Henry Morgenthau to Major., 2-3-1927 (Box 8)
  - D. Roper to Miss Morgan to Mr. Putnam., 2-3-1927 (Box 8)
  - Frank J. G_ to Major Putnam., 2-4-1927 (Box 8)
  - Clarence Gardner for Mr. Bok to Mr. Putnam., 2-4-1927 (Box 8)
  - Henry G. Leach to Major Putnam., 2-4-1927 (Box 8)
  - Chauncey H. Depew to Major Putnam., 2-4-1927 (Box 8)
  - Elmer E. Brown to Major Putnam., 2-5-1927 (Box 8)
  - Henry Osborn Taylor to Putnam., 2-5-1927 (Box 8)
  - From Charles Seymour to Mr. Putnam., 2-7-1927 (Box 8)
  - Henry van Dyke to Major Putnam., 2-7-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Professor Robert G. Cadwell., 2-7-1927 (Box 8)
  - John A. Stewart to Major Putnam., 2-8-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to E. B. Richman., 2-8-1927 (Box 8)
  - Charles Seymour to Putnam., 2-9-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to John A. Stewart., 2-9-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Professor Paul van Dyke., 2-9-1927 (Box 8)
  - (Putnam's secretary) to Lord Loch., 2-9-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Hon. James M. Beck., 2-9-1927 (Box 8)
  - Loch to Major Putnam., 2-10-1927 (Box 8)
  - (Putnam's Secretary) to Sir Gregory Foster., 2-10-1927 (Box 8)
  - Cyrus H. McCormick to Mr. Putnam., 2-10-1927 (Box 8)
  - Frederick Law Olmsted to Cousin Haven., 2-11-1927 (Box 8)
  - I. B. Richman to Major Putnam to Major Putnam., 2-12-1927 (Box 8)
  - Henry R. Shipman to Putnam., 2-13-1927 (Box 8)
  - Charles Wellford Leavitt and Son to Major Putnam., 2-15-1927 (Box 8)
  - Marguerite Deterling to Major Putnam., 2-15-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Frederick Law Olmsted., 2-17-1927 (Box 8)
  - S. Stanwood Menken to Major Putnam., 2-19-1927 (Box 8)
  - Helen Grace Smith to Major Putnam., 2-20-1927 (Box 8)
  - W. H. Baldwin to Major Putnam., 2-21-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Otto H. Kahn., 2-23-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Frederick Law Olmsted., 2-23-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Prof. Alfred N. Whitehead., 2-23-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to W. H. Baldwin, Jr., 2-23-1927 (Box 8)
  - Secretary to Mr. Paul M. Warburg to Putnam., 2-24-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Rollo Ogden., 2-24-1927 (Box 8)
  - Otto Kahn to Putnam., 2-24-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Kahn., 2-25-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Lord Loch., 2-25-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Dr. Butler., 2-25-1927 (Box 8)
  - I. W. Daltman to Major Putnam., 2-26-1927 (Box 8)
  - A. A. Marratt to Major Putnam., 2-26-1927 (Box 8)
  - From Horace D. Taft to Major Putnam., 2-27-1927 (Box 8)
  - R. C. Lattie to Coison (?) to George., 2-28-1927 (Box 8)
  - A. M. Murphy to Putnam., 2-28-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Editor of the Review of Reviews., 2-28-1927 (Box 8)
  - Mortimer L. Schiff to Mr. Putnam., 2-28-1927 (Box 8)
  - Henry L. Stinson to Major Putnam., 2-28-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Otto H. Kahn., 2-28-1927 (Box 8)
  - Laurence M. Larson to Mr. Putnam., 2-28-1927 (Box 8)
  - W. R. Whitney to Mr. Putnam., 2-28-1927 (Box 8)
  - Franklin H. Giddings to Major Putnam., 2-28-1927 (Box 8)
  - A. C. Flick to Major Putnam., 2-28-1927 (Box 8)
  - Magnus W. Alexander to Major Putnam., 3-1-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Professor Charles Seymour., 3-1-1927 (Box 8)
  - J. R. de la Torre Sueno for W. H. Nichols, Jr. to Putnam., 3-1-1927 (Box 8)
  - W. H. P. Faunce to Putnam., 3-2-1927 (Box 8)
  - Isaiah Borman to Major., 3-2-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Professor Laurence M. Larson., 3-2-1927 (Box 8)
  - Dorothy Mills to Major Putnam., 3-2-1927 (Box 8)
  - John Daniels to Major Putnam., 3-3-1927 (Box 8)
  - William Jay Schieffelin to Major., 3-3-1927 (Box 8)
  - A. R. Emanuel for Felix M. Warburg to Putnam., 3-4-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to John Daniels., 3-4-1927 (Box 8)
  - Henry S. Canby to Major Putnam., 3-4-1927 (Box 8)
  - Worthington C. Ford to Major Putnam., 3-4-1927 (Box 8)
  - O. P. Chitwood to Major Putnam., 3-5-1927 (Box 8)
  - Halford L. Hoskins to Major Putnam., 3-5-1927 (Box 8)
  - R. D. Hetzel to Major Putnam., 3-5-1927 (Box 8)
  - Mary E. Woolley to Dr. Putnam., 3-5-1927 (Box 8)
  - William Spence Robertson to Mr. Putnam., 3-6-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Professor Cecil Russell Fish., 3-7-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Mary E. Woolley., 3-7-1927 (Box 8)
  - C. C. Bickel to Putnam., 3-7-1927 (Box 8)
  - George W. Rightmire to Mr. Putnam., 3-7-1927 (Box 8)
  - James M. Thomas to Major Putnam., 3-7-1927 (Box 8)
  - W. H. Siebert to Major Putnam., 3-7-1927 (Box 8)
  - George D. Olde to Major Putnam., 3-8-1927 (Box 8)
  - Marion Edwards Park to Mr. Putnam., 3-9-1927 (Box 8)
  - L. D. Coffman to Mr. Putnam., 3-10-1927 (Box 8)
  - George McAneny to Uncle Haven., 3-10-1927 (Box 8)
  - Ada Comstock to Mr. Putnam., 3-11-1927 (Box 8)
  - Roy Lyman Wilbur to Mr. Putnam., 3-12-1927 (Box 8)
  - Otto Kahn to Mr. Putnam., 3-12-1927 (Box 8)
  - Fredrick C. Hicks to Major Putnam., 3-14-1927 (Box 8)
  - W. H. Campbell to Major Putnam., 3-14-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Stephen P. Duggan., 3-14-1927 (Box 8)
  - George Gordon Battle to Major Putnam., 3-15-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Lord Loch., 3-15-1927 (Box 8)
  - David Kinley to Major Putnam., 3-15-1927 (Box 8)
  - S. P. Duggan to Major Putnam., 3-17-1927 (Box 8)
  - Frederic L. Thompson to Mr. Putnam., 3-17-1927 (Box 8)
  - H. N. MacCracken to Mr. Putnam to Mr. Putnam., 3-16-1927 (Box 8)
  - Stewart L. Mims to Mr. Putnam., 3-17-1927 (Box 8)
  - M. G. Jackson to Putnam., 3-17-1927 (Box 8)
  - E. F. Pemberton to Mr. Putnam., 3-21-1927 (Box 8)
  - H. McD. Clokie to Putnam., 3-21-1927 (Box 8)
  - W. H. Baldwin to Major Putnam., 3-21-1927 (Box 8)
  - H. A. Garfield to Major Putnam., 3-22-1927 (Box 8)
  - James Speyer to Major Putnam., 3-23-1927 (Box 8)
  - Frederick Law Olmsted to Major Putnam., 3-23-1927 (Box 8)
  - Elihu Root to Major., 3-26-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Lady Astor., 3-30-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Olmstead., 3-30-1927 (Box 8)
  - Logan Hay to Major., 3-31-1927 (Box 8)
  - Mrs. Henry Wise Miiller to Mr. Putnam., 4-6-1927 (Box 8)
  - H. I. Perkins to Putnam., 4-6-1927 (Box 8)
  - Anson Phelps Stokes to Mr. Putnam., 4-8-1927 (Box 8)
  - Loch to Major Putnam., 4-9-1927 (Box 8)
  - Winifred C. C_llis to Mr. Putnam., 4-10-1927 (Box 8)
  - Geoffrey Dawson to Mr. Putnam., 4-10-1927 (Box 8)
  - Gertrude D. Stewart to Putnam., 4-12-1927 (Box 8)
  - J. L. Garvin to Major Putnam., 4-13-1927 (Box 8)
  - J. Garnett Lomax to Mr. Putnam., 4-13-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Lord Loch., 4-14-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Harry Harkness Flagler., 4-13-1927 (Box 8)
  - Margret Fiske to Mr. Putnam., 4-14-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Professor Robert McRiroy., 4-16-1927 (Box 8)
  - Reginald E. Weller to Putnam., 4-18-1927 (Box 8)
  - W. A. White to Mr. Putnam., 4-19-1927 (Box 8)
  - George Wharten Pepper to Major Putnam., 4-19-1927 (Box 8)
  - Glenn Frank to Major Putnam., 4-20-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Henry S. Pritchett., 4-20-1927 (Box 8)
  - Elihu Root to Major., 4-20-1927 (Box 8)
  - Ellen F. Pendleton to Major Putnam., 4-21-1927 (Box 8)
  - From Putnam to William H. Baldwin., 4-21-1927 (Box 8)
  - Charles F. (?)hwing to Major Putnam., 4-22-1927 (Box 8)
  - John Daniels to Major Putnam., 4-22-1927 (Box 8)
  - Henry A. Lit_ty to Major Putnam., 4-22-1927 (Box 8)
  - William H. Baldwin to Major Putnam., 4-22-1927 (Box 8)
  - H. G. Leach to Major Putnam., 4-22-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to J. L. Garvin., 4-23-1927 (Box 8)
  - Professor James T. Shotwall to Mr. Putnam., 4-23-1927 (Box 8)
  - Prof. L. J. Paetow to Mr. Putnam., 4-23-1927 (Box 8)
  - Sam Ney to Mr. Putnam., 4-25-1927 (Box 8)
  - F. D. Keppel to Major Putnam., 4-25-1927 (Box 8)
  - David Y. Thomas to Mr. Putnam., 4-25-1927 (Box 8)
  - John Daniels to Major Putnam., 4-25-1927 (Box 8)
  - Carl Russell Fish to Major Putnam., 4-25-1927 (Box 8)
  - F. P. Keppel to Major Putnam., 4-25-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Samuela Rea., 4-27-1927 (Box 8)
  - Philip Kerr to Mr. Putnam., 4-27-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to William R. Baldwin., 4-27-1927 (Box 8)
  - H. Beller to Major Putnam., 4-29-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Professor Fish., 4-29-1927 (Box 8)
  - From the Viconnaess (?) Bryce., 5-7-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Professor C. H. Vantyne., 5-11-1927 (Box 8)
  - Loch to Major Putnam., 5-12-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Lord Lee., 5-12-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Viscount Lee., 5-12-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Mrs. Reid., 5-12-1927 (Box 8)
  - Lord Loch to Major Putnam., 5-16-1927 (Box 8)
  - Lee of Fareham to Major putnam., 5-16-1927 (Box 8)
  - John Daniels to Major Putnam., 5-16-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Lady Bryce., 5-18-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Mrs. Stephan Loines., 5-18-1927 (Box 8)
  - E. Marion Bryce to Major Putnam., 5-19-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Lord Charnwood., 5-21-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Sir John Murray., 5-25-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Lord Loch., 5-25-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Canon Carnegie., 5-25-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Alanson Bigelow Houghton., 5-26-1927 (Box 8)
  - L. Winterbottom to Putnam., 5-26-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Sir Ernest Benn., 5-26-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Sir Otto Bait., 5-27-1927 (Box 8)
  - John Murray to Putnam., 5-27-1927 (Box 8)
  - Gregory Foster to Major Putnam., 5-30-1927 (Box 8)
  - W. E. Carnegie to Major Putnam., 6-1-1927 (Box 8)
  - Ernest Benn to Major Putnam., 6-7-1927 (Box 8)
  - George Sutton to Major Putnam., 6-8-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to H. A. L. Fisher., 6-11-1927 (Box 8)
  - William Cabell Bruce to Mr. Putnam., 6-11-1927 (Box 8)
  - Elisabeth M. Reid to Major Putnam., 6-16-1927 (Box 8)
  - Belfor to Mr. Putnam., 6-16-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to T. W. Lamont., 6-22-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to William B. Baldwin., 6-23-1927 (Box 8)
  - Putnam to Sir Gregory Foster., 6-28-1927 (Box 8)
  - Raymond B. Fosdick to Mr. Putnam., 6-28-1927 (Box 8)